

## Nayeli A. Pérez T. DESIGN + PHOTOGRAPHY

nayeliperez.com

nayeliaperezt@gmail.com  $(915)449 \cdot 3373$ 

San Antonio, TX

in /nayelip

nayeliprz11

Hello! My name is Nayeli Pérez; nice to meet you. I am a multidisciplinary designer with a keen interest in user interface design, front-end development, and the overall challenge of designing digital experiences in an increasingly digital world. I also particularly enjoy the challenges of branding/identity design and design systems.

### **EDUCATION**

AUG 2012 - MAY 2016 Bachelors of Arts in Communication, CUM LAUDE

Minor in Studio Art & Art History -

**Photography Concentration** 

Trinity University - San Antonio, TX

FALL 2015 Study Abroad

Studio Art Centers International (SACI) - Florence, Italy

### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

AUG 2013 - DEC 2015 Photographer

Trinity University Campus Publications - San Antonio, TX

JAN 2015 - MAY 2016 Graphic Design Intern

Trinity University Press - San Antonio, TX

JAN 2016 - MAY 2016 Art Director

Trinity University's Skyline 2016 Magazine - San Antonio, TX

AUG 2016 - PRESENT Head of Design

esd & associates Digital Marketing - San Antonio, TX

#### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish & English **Native Speaker** 

# **SKILLS**

InDesign

Photoshop

Illustrator

Lightroom

**AfterEffects** 

Sketch

Figma

Invision

Wordpress

HTML/CSS

**Bootstrap** 

Javascript

**Extensive Photography** and Darkroom Printing experience